<?xml version="1.1" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<users>
	<user id="1">
		<firstname>Kevin</firstname>
		<lastname>Hart</lastname>
		<birthdate>19790706</birthdate>
		<bio>
			Hart is an actor and producer, known for Kevin Hart: Let Me Explain (2013), 
			Ride Along (2014) and The Wedding Ringer (2015). He was previously married 
			to Torrei Hart.
		</bio>
	</user>
	<user id="2">
		<firstname>Russell</firstname>
		<lastname>Peters</lastname>
		<birthdate>19700929</birthdate>
		<bio>
			Peters is an actor and producer, known for Source Code (2011), Russell 
			Peters: The Green Card Tour - Live from The O2 Arena (2011) and Russell 
			Peters: Two Concerts, One Ticket (2006).
		</bio>
	</user>
	<user id="3">
		<firstname>Will</firstname>
		<lastname>Ferrell</lastname>
		<birthdate>19790716</birthdate>
		<bio>
			A graduate of the University of Southern California, Ferrell became interested 
			in performing while a student at University High School in Irvine, where he 
			made his school's daily morning announcements over the public address system 
			in disguised voices. He started as a member of the Los Angeles comedy/improvisation 
			group The Groundlings, where fellow cast members Ana Gasteyer, Maya Rudolph and 
			former Saturday Night Live (1975) repertory players such as Laraine Newman, 
			Jon Lovitz and Phil Hartman began their careers. It was there he met Chris 
			Kattan and the two became good friends and both went on to Saturday Night Live 
			(1975) later. He has also appeared on several television programs, including 
			Strangers with Candy (1999), Grace Under Fire (1993) and Living Single (1993) 
			during his time at The Groundlings. Will also lent his voice to the armless 
			and legless dad of cartoon family "The Oblongs".
		</bio>
	</user>
	<user id="4">
		<firstname>Ben</firstname>
		<lastname>Stiller</lastname>
		<birthdate>19651130</birthdate>
		<bio>
			Before he even got his start in Hollywood, Ben put in several consistently solid 
			years in the theater. After dropping out of UCLA, he performed in the Tony Award 
			winner, "The House of Blue Leaves". While working on the play, Stiller shot a 
			short spoof of The Color of Money (1986) starring him (in the Tom Cruise role) 
			and his American Playhouse: The House of Blue Leaves (1987) costar John Mahoney 
			(in the Paul Newman role). The short film was so funny that Lorne Michaels purchased 
			it and aired it on Saturday Night Live (1975). This led to Ben spending a year on 
			the show in 1989.
		</bio>
	</user>
	<user id="5">
		<firstname>Chris</firstname>
		<lastname>Pratt</lastname>
		<birthdate>19792106</birthdate>
		<bio>
			Christopher Michael Pratt is an American film and television actor. Pratt played 
			major supporting roles in several television series, including Everwood (2002), 
			The O.C. (2003), and Parks and Recreation (2009), and notable film roles in Moneyball 
			(2011), The Five-Year Engagement (2012), Zero Dark Thirty (2012), and Delivery Man 
			(2013). In 2014, he broke out after headlining two of the year's biggest films: he 
			voiced the lead, Emmet Brickowoski, in The Lego Movie (2014), and starred as Peter 
			Quill in Guardians of the Galaxy (2014). In 2015, he headlined the sci-fi thriller 
			Jurassic World (2015), and began filming on the western remake The Magnificent Seven 
			(2017), with Denzel Washington and Ethan Hawke.
		</bio>
	</user>
	<user id="6">
		<firstname>Winter Ave</firstname>
		<lastname>Zoli</lastname>
		<birthdate>19800330</birthdate>
		<bio>
			Winter Ave Zoli was born in New Hope, Pennsylvania. At the age of 11, she moved with 
			her family to Prague, Czech Republic, where she was able to fully plant her Czech roots 
			from her fathers side of the family. She studied middle school and high school at the 
			International School of Prague. She transitioned her way from ballet to musical theater, 
			developing a love for the stage, and for the craft of acting. She began working 
			professionally at the age of 13, and developed her resume through acting opportunities 
			on European and American productions that came through Prague. At 17, she attended the 
			Carnegie-Mellon summer school theater program, and at 19 enrolled in the Atlantic Theater 
			Company acting school in New York city, founded by playwright David Mamet, and actor 
			William H. Macy. After graduating from the professional program, Winter moved to Los Angeles, 
			where she resides. Besides acting, her most beloved moments come from horse back 
			riding, yoga, and running in the canyons of Los Angeles.
		</bio>
	</user>
	<user id="7">
		<firstname>Taylor</firstname>
		<lastname>Schilling</lastname>
		<birthdate>19840727</birthdate>
		<bio>
			Taylor Schilling was born in Boston, Massachusetts. Her father, Robert, is a former 
			prosecutor, and her mother, Patricia "Tish" (Miller), works in administration at MIT. 
			Taylor attended Wayland High School, but graduated from West Roxbury High School in 
			2002, and made her film debut in Dark Matter (2007). She starred in the movies Atlas 
			Shrugged: Part I (2011) and The Lucky One (2012), and has a role in director Ben Affleck's 
			Argo (2012).
		</bio>
	</user>
</users>