<?xml version="1.1" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<users>
	<user>
		<id>1</id>
		<firstname>Kevin</firstname>
		<lastname>Hart</lastname>
		<birthdate>19790706</birthdate>
		<bio>
			Hart is an actor and producer, known for Kevin Hart: Let Me Explain (2013), 
			Ride Along (2014) and The Wedding Ringer (2015). He was previously married 
			to Torrei Hart.
		</bio>
	</user>
	<user>
		<id>2</id>
		<firstname>Russell</firstname>
		<lastname>Peters</lastname>
		<birthdate>19700929</birthdate>
		<bio>
			Peters is an actor and producer, known for Source Code (2011), Russell 
			Peters: The Green Card Tour - Live from The O2 Arena (2011) and Russell 
			Peters: Two Concerts, One Ticket (2006).
		</bio>
	</user>
	<user>
		<id>3</id>
		<firstname>Will</firstname>
		<lastname>Ferrell</lastname>
		<birthdate>19790716</birthdate>
		<bio>
			A graduate of the University of Southern California, Ferrell became interested 
			in performing while a student at University High School in Irvine, where he 
			made his school's daily morning announcements over the public address system 
			in disguised voices. He started as a member of the Los Angeles comedy/improvisation 
			group The Groundlings, where fellow cast members Ana Gasteyer, Maya Rudolph and 
			former Saturday Night Live (1975) repertory players such as Laraine Newman, 
			Jon Lovitz and Phil Hartman began their careers. It was there he met Chris 
			Kattan and the two became good friends and both went on to Saturday Night Live 
			(1975) later. He has also appeared on several television programs, including 
			Strangers with Candy (1999), Grace Under Fire (1993) and Living Single (1993) 
			during his time at The Groundlings. Will also lent his voice to the armless 
			and legless dad of cartoon family "The Oblongs".
		</bio>
	</user>
	<user>
		<id>4</id>
		<firstname>Ben</firstname>
		<lastname>Stiller</lastname>
		<birthday>19651130</birthday>
		<bio>
			Before he even got his start in Hollywood, Ben put in several consistently solid 
			years in the theater. After dropping out of UCLA, he performed in the Tony Award 
			winner, "The House of Blue Leaves". While working on the play, Stiller shot a 
			short spoof of The Color of Money (1986) starring him (in the Tom Cruise role) 
			and his American Playhouse: The House of Blue Leaves (1987) costar John Mahoney 
			(in the Paul Newman role). The short film was so funny that Lorne Michaels purchased 
			it and aired it on Saturday Night Live (1975). This led to Ben spending a year on 
			the show in 1989.
		</bio>
	</user>
</users>